曲：广东雨神
qū ： guǎng dōng yǔ shén
Composed by: Guangdong Yu Shen
安静地离去
ān jìng de lí qù
Quietly leaving
和孤单一起
hé gū dān yì qǐ
Together with the loneliness
拥挤的回忆时间抹去
yōng jǐ de huí yì shí jiān mǒ qù
Crowded memories erased by time
人在广东已经漂泊十年
rén zài guǎng dōng yǐ jīng piāo bó shí nián
I've been drifting in Guangdong for ten years now
有时也怀念当初一起
yǒu shí yě huái niàn dāng chū yì qǐ
Sometimes I still miss how we once were together
经已改变
jīng yǐ gǎi biàn
Everything has already changed
让这天空将你我相连
ràng zhè tiān kōng jiāng nǐ wǒ xiāng lián
Let this sky connect you and me
怀念你走了云的天空还任性
huái niàn nǐ zǒu le yún de tiān kōng hái rèn xìng
Missing you—you've gone, and the clouded sky still acts on its whims
是否它相信在乎
shì fǒu tā xiāng xìn zài hū
Does it believe, does it care
反而容易放弃
fǎn ér róng yì fàng qì
Or does it give up all too easily
非要最后一无所有
fēi yào zuì hòu yī wú suǒ yǒu
Insisting on ending up with nothing at all
才无所畏惧
cái wú suǒ wèi jù
Only then does it fear nothing
我知道好多时候
wǒ zhī dào hǎo duō shí hòu
I know that so much of the time
爱一个人是没任何理由的
ài yí gè rén shì méi rèn hé lǐ yóu de
Loving someone needs no reason at all
你同其他女子不一样的
nǐ tóng qí tā nǚ zǐ bù yí yàng de
You're not like any of the other girls
你从来都不问我钟意你什么
nǐ cóng lái dōu bù wèn wǒ zhōng yì nǐ shén me
You never once ask me what I love about you
反而我成日都问你
fǎn ér wǒ chéng rì dōu wèn nǐ
Yet I'm the one asking you all day long
你究竟钟意我什么
nǐ jiū jìng zhōng yì wǒ shén me
What on earth do you even like about me
笑的多一些改变要彻底
xiào de duō yī xiē gǎi biàn yào chè dǐ
Smile a little more—the change has to be complete
直面这世界真假游戏
zhí miàn zhè shì jiè zhēn jiǎ yóu xì
Facing head-on this world's game of truth and lies
人在广东已经漂泊十年
rén zài guǎng dōng yǐ jīng piāo bó shí nián
I've been drifting in Guangdong for ten years now
有时也怀念当初一起
yǒu shí yě huái niàn dāng chū yì qǐ
Sometimes I still miss how we once were together
经已改变
jīng yǐ gǎi biàn
Everything has already changed
让这天空将你我相连
ràng zhè tiān kōng jiāng nǐ wǒ xiāng lián
Let this sky connect you and me
怀念你走了云的天空还任性
huái niàn nǐ zǒu le yún de tiān kōng hái rèn xìng
Missing you—you've gone, and the clouded sky still acts on its whims
是否它相信下一次的相遇
shì fǒu tā xiāng xìn xià yī cì de xiāng yù
Does it believe in the next time we'll meet
就算最后一无所有
jiù suàn zuì hòu yī wú suǒ yǒu
Even if I end up with nothing at all
也无所畏惧
yě wú suǒ wèi jù
I'll still fear nothing
相信你就如当初一起
xiāng xìn nǐ jiù rú dāng chū yì qǐ
Believing in you, just like when we were first together
行过广东这十年幸福走了
xíng guò guǎng dōng zhè shí nián xìng fú zǒu le
Walking through these ten years in Guangdong, the happiness has gone
唏嘘感慨那当初
xī xū gǎn kǎi nà dāng chū
Sighing with regret over how it all began
相信你哪怕坚强
xiāng xìn nǐ nǎ pà jiān qiáng
Believing in you—even if your strength
是假装出勇敢的面具
shì jiǎ zhuāng chū yǒng gǎn de miàn jù
Is just a mask of pretended bravery
也不能少活得精彩的勇气
yě bù néng shǎo huó dé jīng cǎi de yǒng qì
You still can't go without the courage to live a vivid life
人在广东已经漂泊十年
rén zài guǎng dōng yǐ jīng piāo bó shí nián
I've been drifting in Guangdong for ten years now
有时也怀念当初一起
yǒu shí yě huái niàn dāng chū yì qǐ
Sometimes I still miss how we once were together
经已改变
jīng yǐ gǎi biàn
Everything has already changed
让这天空将你我相连
ràng zhè tiān kōng jiāng nǐ wǒ xiāng lián
Let this sky connect you and me
怀念你走了云的天空
huái niàn nǐ zǒu le yún de tiān kōng
Missing you—you've gone, and the clouded sky
还任性是否它相信
hái rèn xìng shì fǒu tā xiāng xìn
Still acts on its whims; does it believe
下一次的相遇
xià yī cì de xiāng yù
In the next time we'll meet
就算最后一无所有
jiù suàn zuì hòu yī wú suǒ yǒu
Even if I end up with nothing at all
也无所畏惧
yě wú suǒ wèi jù
I'll still fear nothing
就算最后一无所有
jiù suàn zuì hòu yī wú suǒ yǒu
Even if I end up with nothing at all
我都无所畏惧
wǒ dōu wú suǒ wèi jù
I'll fear nothing at all